[
    {
        "question" : "1. Who translated the Book of Mormon?",
        "options" : ["Mormon","Moroni","Nefi","Joseph Smith"],
        "answer" : 3,
        "track" : "Check the Introduccion the Book of Mormon"
    },
    {
        "question" : "2. Who demanded a sign from Alma the Younger?",
        "options" : ["Ammon", "Helaman","Korihor","Zerahemnah"],
        "answer" : 2,
        "track" : "Check Alma 30:43"
    },
    {
        "question" : "3. What is the longest chapter in the Book of Mormon?",
        "options" : ["Jacob 5","2 Nephi 31","Omni 1","Alma 63"],
        "answer" : 1,
        "track" : "Read each chapter if necessary"
    },
    {
        "question" : "4. who was not a witness to the book of mormon",
        "options" : ["David Withmer","Martin Harris","Emma Smith","Oliver Cowdery"],
        "answer" : 1,
        "track" : "Check the witness testimony"
    },
    {
        "question" : "5. Besides Ether, who were the last two survivors of the Jaredite Nation?",
        "options" : ["Coriantumr y Shiz","Coriantumr y Zoram","Shiz y Korihor","Shiz y Zoram"],
        "answer" : 0,
        "track" : "Check Ether 15:29-30"
    },
    {
        "question" : "6. Who compiled the golden plates?",
        "options" : ["Alma","Nephi","Mormon","Moroni"],
        "answer" : 2,
        "track" : "Check the Title page of the Book Mormon"
    },
    {
        "question" : "7. Cuantos libros tiene el libro de morm√≥n?",
        "options" : ["11","15","12","24"],
        "answer" : 1,
        "track" : "Check the Book of Mormon index"
    },
    {
        "question" : "8. In which chapter is the vision that Lehi had of the tree of life found?",
        "options" : ["1 Nephi 1","Jacob 5","1 Nephi 8","Alma 15"],
        "answer" : 2,
        "track" : "Read each chapter if necessary"
    },
    {
        "question" : "9. Which prophet repented upon hearing Abinadi's words?",
        "options" : ["Alma","Amulek","Enos","Ammon"],
        "answer" : 0,
        "track" : "Check Mosiah 17"
    },
    {
        "question" : "10. Who was left mute as a sign of God's power?",
        "options" : ["Nehor","Zeezrom","Gadianton","Korihor"],
        "answer" : 3,
        "track" : "Check Alma 30"
    }
]